<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DataSea Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DataSea Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2017, Robin Browne; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot Composition in ggplot</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/12/29/ggplot_composition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/12/29/ggplot_composition/</guid>
      <description>I recently came across a tweet by Mara Averick where she talked about patchwork, a library to help you arrange your ggplot outputs.
Some fresh viz ✨ magic from @thomasp85
&amp;quot;patchwork: the composer of ggplots&amp;quot; https://t.co/FtSNVDmV42 #rstats #ggplot2 #dataviz pic.twitter.com/wjb4xJcF2W
&amp;mdash; Mara Averick (@dataandme) December 6, 2017  A Basic ExampleFrom Thomas’ Github page:
Load Library library(ggplot2)library(patchwork)library(dplyr)Output p1 &amp;lt;- ggplot(mtcars) + geom_point(aes(mpg, disp))p2 &amp;lt;- ggplot(mtcars) + geom_boxplot(aes(gear, disp, group = gear))p1 + p2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Analytics API: Automated Segment Generation</title>
      <link>/blog/2017/12/26/adobe_analytics-auto_generate_segments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2017/12/26/adobe_analytics-auto_generate_segments/</guid>
      <description>For any given site, you would typically have many content groups. For example, you are a car manufacturer, and your site has car models that covers a range in the market. How would you see the overlap in interest between your different car models?
Adobe Analytics’ workspace feature allows you to create segment overlap report to see how the users are converging. But unfortunately, you can only do 3 segments, and cannot easily generate n combinations of segments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Are you curious about something? Do you have some kind of problem with our products? As am hastily invited settled at limited civilly fortune me. Really spring in extent an by. Judge but built gay party world. Of so am he remember although required. Bachelor unpacked be advanced at. Confined in declared marianne is vicinity.
Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24&amp;frasl;7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>